

Matheus Gonzalez, #OPEN_TO_WORK Machine Learning Engineer | MLOps | Data Freelancer

São Paulo, São Paulo **Telefone:** +55 11 99021-3656

RESUMO

With over 13 years of experience, I've shaped my career at the intersection of Software Development and Machine Learning, helping companies optimize their infrastructure and unlock potential through data, resulting in increased revenue and greater operational efficiency.

Key Competencies: MLOps, Software Engineering, Python, Spark, SQL, Azure, GCP, AWS, Databricks, Docker, Airflow, MLflow, Looker Studio

FORMAÇÃO

- Extensão, Mineração de Dados Complexos 01/2021 01/2021 Universidade Estadual de Campinas
- SHIFT, Machine learning e Data mining 01/2019 01/2019 FIAP
- Pós graduação/MBA em MBA em Big Data (Data Science), Big Data, Data Science, Hadoop, Spark 01/2018 - 01/2019
- Tecnólogo em Tecnólogo, Análise e Desenvolvimento de Sistemas 01/2011 01/2014
 Fatec Garça

EXPERIÊNCIAS

ML Optimize 01/2023 - Atual

Machine Learning Engineering Consultant

At ML Optimize, I understand the importance of deploying machine learning models to drive business success. As a leading MLOps and Data Engineering consultant, I work with businesses like yours to build a robust and scalable data infrastructure that enables you to deploy and manage ML models in production with ease.

With my expertise, you can accelerate your business by unlocking the full potential of your data. Whether you're looking to improve operational efficiency, increase revenue, or enhance customer experiences, I am here to help.

Let's work together to build a winning data strategy that drives your business forward.. Competências: Aprendizado de máquina \cdot Natural Language Processing (NLP) \cdot Gestão de projetos \cdot Engenharia de dados \cdot MLOps

• BlueShift Brasil 06/2022 - 12/2022

Senior Machine Learning Engineer

Competências: Artificial Intelligence (AI) · Aprendizado de máquina · Pattern Recognition · Communication · Pattern Recognition · Pa

Data Science · Computer Science

• BlueShift Brasil 06/2021 - 06/2022

Machine Learning Engineer

Led the design, construction, and documentation of complete ML lifecycles, including Feature Store and production monitoring, significantly contributing to the success of major clients like Natura and Porto Seguro.. Competências: Azure Databricks · Feature Store · MLOps · Amazon SageMaker · Amazon Elastic MapReduce (EMR) · Apache Airflow · MLflow · PySpark · Machine Learning · Data Engeneering

• SKY Brasil 07/2020 - 05/2021

Machine Learning Engineer

Developed crucial ingestion pipelines to expedite the ML lifecycle, streamlining processes, and enhancing operational efficiency.. Competências: PL/SQL · MLOps · Amazon Elastic MapReduce (EMR) · PySpark · Python · AWS · Data Science · Machine Learning

Trackmob 04/2019 - 06/2020

Data Scientist

As a Data Scientist, I builded end-to-end ML solutions, since ingestion pipeline until deploy ML models.

I also worked with customer segmentation, churn analysis, unsupervised topic modeling of customer questions (tf-idf, LDA), data viz, web crawlers and D.W. modeling.. Competências: Análise de dados · Scikit-Learn · MLOps · Amazon QuickSight · AWS Glue · Natural Language Processing (NLP) · PySpark · Data Science · Amazon S3 · Machine Learning

Arquimedesx 06/2018 - 03/2019

Data Engineer

As a Data Engineer, I've design, plan and build data lakes and pipelines for ingestions data streaming.. Competências: $PL/SQL \cdot GCP$ Data $Proc \cdot Artificial$ Intelligence (AI) \cdot Google Cloud Platform (GCP) \cdot Communication \cdot NLP \cdot PySpark \cdot Python \cdot Spark Streaming do Apache \cdot Data Science \cdot Computer Science \cdot Google BigQuery

MarketUP 12/2017 - 06/2018

Web Developer

Competências: SQL · C# · API REST · CSS · AWS · ASP.NET MVC · Computer Science · HTML5

• Liberty Seguros Brasil 01/2017 - 11/2017

Web Developer & CI/CD Lead

As a CI/CD Lead, I contributed to turn simple some complex process through CI/CD tools.. Competências: $SQL \cdot WebDriver\ Selenium \cdot Jenkins \cdot C\# \cdot CSS \cdot ASP.NET\ MVC \cdot Computer\ Science \cdot HTML5$

Função Sistemas - PÁGINA OFICIAL 03/2016 - 01/2017

Web Developer

Competências: SQL · ASP.NET · VB.NET · HTML · CSS

• FRG Tecnologia 06/2014 - 03/2016

Web Developer

Competências: PL/SQL · C# · HTML · CSS · ASP.NET MVC

MicroCS 08/2012 - 06/2014

Software Developer

Competências: PL/SQL · VB.NET

Dataplace Business Solutions 02/2012 - 08/2012

Trainee Developer

• Centro Paula Souza - Fatec Garça 08/2011 - 12/2011

Algorithms Monitor

Competências: C++ · Programming Logic